{
    "id": "3e731a74c070489fbaa688d2d4db0a6d",
    "title": "Like And As",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She behaves …………………. a spoilt brat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a16e78b581b247a992e06685c54bc574"
        },
        {
            "question": "A crocodile starts life …………………. an egg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5021f64a137440f2bdfa08c1da33efca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He drinks …………………. a fish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "678c956602f84cc4b9b1ca258cab6e2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody loves her ……………….. I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49888b28208d4847909b27e32490781e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an alcoholic, ……………….. were most of his friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10bb4358ccc84c8c9428996cf65e3a57"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you behave ………………… a child?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6796b7363a804b1aa3040061052f2475"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked …………………. a waiter for two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ceeb66ef66d34a8eb1b46bfdf16e09c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ……………….. her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "75514cc05bfb4ce8a30cf4e84444a81a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good at scientific subjects ………………….. physics and chemistry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d3bf884ffdb42318b2470b46912fae3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will do it, …………………. agreed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24ec537569c54245b75cc86201d5176d"
        }
    ]
}